[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 7, "question": "Did you imagine ever working for him?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "imagine", "ever", "working", "for", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 8, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 10, "question": "But who's the real Newt Gingrich?", "question_tokens": ["But", "who", "'s", "the", "real", "Newt", "Gingrich", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 11, "answer": "This inner intensity that I have tended to, in some ways, be destructive.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "inner", "intensity", "that", "I", "have", "tended", "to", ",", "in", "some", "ways", ",", "be", "destructive", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Newt Gingrich"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 22, "question": "Why here?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 23, "answer": "It's fun.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "fun", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "Yours?", "question_tokens": ["Yours", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "Any super PAC.", "answer_tokens": ["Any", "super", "PAC", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "Yours or Mitt Romney's secret super PAC?", "question_tokens": ["Yours", "or", "Mitt", "Romney", "'s", "secret", "super", "PAC", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "Any.", "answer_tokens": ["Any", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "So where did Saint Newt come from?", "question_tokens": ["So", "where", "did", "Saint", "Newt", "come", "from", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "It's not a question about being Saint Newt, it's a question about where you're prepared to fight.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "a", "question", "about", "being", "Saint", "Newt", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "question", "about", "where", "you", "'re", "prepared", "to", "fight", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJR", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "If you'd known what was coming?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "'d", "known", "what", "was", "coming", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "Well, probably I would have reacted earlier to the attack ads, especially the ones that were untrue.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "probably", "I", "would", "have", "reacted", "earlier", "to", "the", "attack", "ads", ",", "especially", "the", "ones", "that", "were", "untrue", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "What's your response to that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "response", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "I like the brilliant visionary part.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "like", "the", "brilliant", "visionary", "part", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "ORGAN: In answer to the too much baggage and the erratic allegations, I mean a bit of truth of both, I would say, wouldn't you?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "In", "answer", "to", "the", "too", "much", "baggage", "and", "the", "erratic", "allegations", ",", "I", "mean", "a", "bit", "of", "truth", "of", "both", ",", "I", "would", "say", ",", "would", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "Well, I think that's part of what I have to overcome.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "'s", "part", "of", "what", "I", "have", "to", "overcome", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "Do you know the answer?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "the", "answer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "Well, the point is, if a guy is running for president -- he has two major credentials, his record as governor which he doesn't want to talk about because he was much more liberal as governor than a Republican primary will ever endorse.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "point", "is", ",", "if", "a", "guy", "is", "running", "for", "president", "--", "he", "has", "two", "major", "credentials", ",", "his", "record", "as", "governor", "which", "he", "does", "n't", "want", "to", "talk", "about", "because", "he", "was", "much", "more", "liberal", "as", "governor", "than", "a", "Republican", "primary", "will", "ever", "endorse", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "But if he manages to establish that his record at Bain was such that he created more jobs than he effectively lost you could argue that's exactly what is needed in America right now in the sense that you're going to have to cut, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["But", "if", "he", "manages", "to", "establish", "that", "his", "record", "at", "Bain", "was", "such", "that", "he", "created", "more", "jobs", "than", "he", "effectively", "lost", "you", "could", "argue", "that", "'s", "exactly", "what", "is", "needed", "in", "America", "right", "now", "in", "the", "sense", "that", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "have", "to", "cut", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "POS", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "But he makes that assertion anyway.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "he", "makes", "that", "assertion", "anyway", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Bain"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", ",", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "-- he was a force for negative?", "question_tokens": ["--", "he", "was", "a", "force", "for", "negative", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "Well, I think we've certainly raised the question -- it's not about capitalism, it's not about free enterprise, it's about values, character and judgment.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "we", "'ve", "certainly", "raised", "the", "question", "--", "it", "'s", "not", "about", "capitalism", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "about", "free", "enterprise", ",", "it", "'s", "about", "values", ",", "character", "and", "judgment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "What do you actually think of him personally as a man?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "actually", "think", "of", "him", "personally", "as", "a", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "You have no view?", "question_tokens": ["You", "have", "no", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "No, I have no view.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "have", "no", "view", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "Do you like him?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "He is a competitor.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "is", "a", "competitor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", ":"], "qSentId": 159, "question": "You don't have to go to the sun to know it's hot, do you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "have", "to", "go", "to", "the", "sun", "to", "know", "it", "'s", "hot", ",", "do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "I'm only saying --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "only", "saying", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "Do you still stand by the fact he's a liar about you?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "still", "stand", "by", "the", "fact", "he", "'s", "a", "liar", "about", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "I still stand by the fact that he is -- that he is not truthful.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "still", "stand", "by", "the", "fact", "that", "he", "is", "--", "that", "he", "is", "not", "truthful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "What do you think of his character?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "his", "character", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "I don't have an obligation to answer any of that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "have", "an", "obligation", "to", "answer", "any", "of", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ":", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 182, "question": "Is it better for a leader, for a potential president of the United States, to admit that they have been wrong and to change their mind about issues, or to stick stubbornly by their same platform on these things decade after decade?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "better", "for", "a", "leader", ",", "for", "a", "potential", "president", "of", "the", "United", "States", ",", "to", "admit", "that", "they", "have", "been", "wrong", "and", "to", "change", "their", "mind", "about", "issues", ",", "or", "to", "stick", "stubbornly", "by", "their", "same", "platform", "on", "these", "things", "decade", "after", "decade", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "CC", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 183, "answer": "If somebody -- first of all, you had a fairly long career.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "somebody", "--", "first", "of", "all", ",", "you", "had", "a", "fairly", "long", "career", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["United States"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "I mean, it would be strange if you hadn't, wouldn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "it", "would", "be", "strange", "if", "you", "had", "n't", ",", "would", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "But are you dubious about Mitt Romney's motivation for changing his position?", "question_tokens": ["But", "are", "you", "dubious", "about", "Mitt", "Romney", "'s", "motivation", "for", "changing", "his", "position", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "Well, first of all, if you go to Romneytaxes.com you'll see every single tax he raised while he's governor.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "if", "you", "go", "to", "Romneytaxes.com", "you", "'ll", "see", "every", "single", "tax", "he", "raised", "while", "he", "'s", "governor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "Could you imagine ever working for him?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "imagine", "ever", "working", "for", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "Can there be a good result?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "there", "be", "a", "good", "result", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "EX", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "If you don't win, given you've set that parameter, do you drop out?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "do", "n't", "win", ",", "given", "you", "'ve", "set", "that", "parameter", ",", "do", "you", "drop", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "Or is that just good politics?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "that", "just", "good", "politics", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "I'm not saying it's his fault or not his fault.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "saying", "it", "'s", "his", "fault", "or", "not", "his", "fault", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "DT", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "Is this the biggest week of your life politically?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "the", "biggest", "week", "of", "your", "life", "politically", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "Yes, I think politically, this -- well, it's the most decisive week.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "think", "politically", ",", "this", "--", "well", ",", "it", "'s", "the", "most", "decisive", "week", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "Is Rick Santorum -- he had the Santorum surge, took a bit of a hit in New Hampshire, not necessarily surprisingly, but is it over for him, or do you think you continue to see him get traction?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "Rick", "Santorum", "--", "he", "had", "the", "Santorum", "surge", ",", "took", "a", "bit", "of", "a", "hit", "in", "New", "Hampshire", ",", "not", "necessarily", "surprisingly", ",", "but", "is", "it", "over", "for", "him", ",", "or", "do", "you", "think", "you", "continue", "to", "see", "him", "get", "traction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "RB", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick Santorum", "Santorum"], "LOCATION": ["New Hampshire"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "Are you surprised Governor Perry is still going?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "surprised", "Governor", "Perry", "is", "still", "going", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "Well, that's his decision.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "his", "decision", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Perry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 300, "question": "At what point does the party have to rally, as you say, behind this one consensus?", "question_tokens": ["At", "what", "point", "does", "the", "party", "have", "to", "rally", ",", "as", "you", "say", ",", "behind", "this", "one", "consensus", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "TO", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 301, "answer": "No, never --", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "never", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "Has it reached that point now?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "it", "reached", "that", "point", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "The party never has to rally.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "party", "never", "has", "to", "rally", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "But doesn't it have to -- doesn't it have to collectively say, \"We're now going to have these two duke it out\"?", "question_tokens": ["But", "does", "n't", "it", "have", "to", "--", "does", "n't", "it", "have", "to", "collectively", "say", ",", "``", "We", "'re", "now", "going", "to", "have", "these", "two", "duke", "it", "out", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "TO", ":", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "RB", "VB", ",", "``", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "RP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "Does it help that you have endless candidates carrying on?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "help", "that", "you", "have", "endless", "candidates", "carrying", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "But that is not the party's function.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "that", "is", "not", "the", "party", "'s", "function", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "Given what you experienced on those battlefields, given what you saw, if you had been the commander-in-chief, that decision about Iraq, would have taken that decision?", "question_tokens": ["Given", "what", "you", "experienced", "on", "those", "battlefields", ",", "given", "what", "you", "saw", ",", "if", "you", "had", "been", "the", "commander-in-chief", ",", "that", "decision", "about", "Iraq", ",", "would", "have", "taken", "that", "decision", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "Well, there were two decisions.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "were", "two", "decisions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iraq"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "You mean with hindsight or without hindsight?", "question_tokens": ["You", "mean", "with", "hindsight", "or", "without", "hindsight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "Well, I'm looking with foresight.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "looking", "with", "foresight", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "And what would do in that circumstance?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "would", "do", "in", "that", "circumstance", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "Well, by then you've already been pushed into a corner where only military action is capable.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "by", "then", "you", "'ve", "already", "been", "pushed", "into", "a", "corner", "where", "only", "military", "action", "is", "capable", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "CC", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "If I said to you, give me a phrase which would sum up your kind of overview of a modern American foreign policy, what would you say it would be?", "question_tokens": ["If", "I", "said", "to", "you", ",", "give", "me", "a", "phrase", "which", "would", "sum", "up", "your", "kind", "of", "overview", "of", "a", "modern", "American", "foreign", "policy", ",", "what", "would", "you", "say", "it", "would", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "I would say it would be to protect the interests of America and her allies, and to do it in as effective a way as possible with the minimum of force and the minimum of risk.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "say", "it", "would", "be", "to", "protect", "the", "interests", "of", "America", "and", "her", "allies", ",", "and", "to", "do", "it", "in", "as", "effective", "a", "way", "as", "possible", "with", "the", "minimum", "of", "force", "and", "the", "minimum", "of", "risk", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "Would you quibble with any of those comparisons?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "quibble", "with", "any", "of", "those", "comparisons", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "No, not much.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "much", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "Why is this not possible now?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "this", "not", "possible", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "It is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "Not Republicans?", "question_tokens": ["Not", "Republicans", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "I think it's the whole system.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "the", "whole", "system", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "TO", "VB", ":", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "Do they underestimate you?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "they", "underestimate", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "I love the capacity of Washington pundits to be -- to be sort of serially wrong, you know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "the", "capacity", "of", "Washington", "pundits", "to", "be", "--", "to", "be", "sort", "of", "serially", "wrong", ",", "you", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "If you were in South Carolina and you're thinking \"should I vote for this guy,\" what is the biggest misconception about you personally?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "in", "South", "Carolina", "and", "you", "'re", "thinking", "``", "should", "I", "vote", "for", "this", "guy", ",", "''", "what", "is", "the", "biggest", "misconception", "about", "you", "personally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "``", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "''", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "Oh, I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["South Carolina"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "How important is your wife to you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "important", "is", "your", "wife", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "Extraordinarily.", "answer_tokens": ["Extraordinarily", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "Are you as happy with Callista as you've ever been with any woman in your life?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "as", "happy", "with", "Callista", "as", "you", "'ve", "ever", "been", "with", "any", "woman", "in", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "Oh, sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Callista"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "Do you accept it's a valid criticism?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "accept", "it", "'s", "a", "valid", "criticism", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "Look, I think people have every right to ask of any presidential candidate virtually everything.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "I", "think", "people", "have", "every", "right", "to", "ask", "of", "any", "presidential", "candidate", "virtually", "everything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Eucharist"]}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", ":", "DT", "NN", ":", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "How has that changed you as a person?", "question_tokens": ["How", "has", "that", "changed", "you", "as", "a", "person", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "There is a power to the Eucharist in the Catholic tradition that is a power to -- the community -- one of the things that the people would say to me is welcome home.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "is", "a", "power", "to", "the", "Eucharist", "in", "the", "Catholic", "tradition", "that", "is", "a", "power", "to", "--", "the", "community", "--", "one", "of", "the", "things", "that", "the", "people", "would", "say", "to", "me", "is", "welcome", "home", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Romney"]}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "Well, I think that that's something that Romney has to be able to explain.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "that", "'s", "something", "that", "Romney", "has", "to", "be", "able", "to", "explain", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "Do you as a Catholic find it strange?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "as", "a", "Catholic", "find", "it", "strange", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "No, I'm not judgmental about how people go to God.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "judgmental", "about", "how", "people", "go", "to", "God", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "If I could be any animal?", "question_tokens": ["If", "I", "could", "be", "any", "animal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "An elephant?", "question_tokens": ["An", "elephant", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "They have 105,000 muscles in their trunk.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "have", "105,000", "muscles", "in", "their", "trunk", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 562, "question": "You want 105,000 muscles in your trunk?", "question_tokens": ["You", "want", "105,000", "muscles", "in", "your", "trunk", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "And they're big and they last a long time.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "they", "'re", "big", "and", "they", "last", "a", "long", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "What kind of animal do you think Mitt Romney would be?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "animal", "do", "you", "think", "Mitt", "Romney", "would", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "I have no idea and I'm not going to go down that road.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "no", "idea", "and", "I", "'m", "not", "going", "to", "go", "down", "that", "road", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 578, "question": "What are the key things that a new president come November, if it is a new president, needs to do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "key", "things", "that", "a", "new", "president", "come", "November", ",", "if", "it", "is", "a", "new", "president", ",", "needs", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 579, "answer": "INGRICH: Well, I think first of all you have to offer an optimistic vision of a hopeful, successful American future.", "answer_tokens": ["INGRICH", ":", "Well", ",", "I", "think", "first", "of", "all", "you", "have", "to", "offer", "an", "optimistic", "vision", "of", "a", "hopeful", ",", "successful", "American", "future", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Korea"]}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "What do you think he would make of the Newt Gingrich that you've become?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "he", "would", "make", "of", "the", "Newt", "Gingrich", "that", "you", "'ve", "become", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "Well, considering that he wrote from Korea after I did my very first newspaper article at 10.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "considering", "that", "he", "wrote", "from", "Korea", "after", "I", "did", "my", "very", "first", "newspaper", "article", "at", "10", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Newt Gingrich"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "Would he prefer the Newt Gingrich today to the one that he found slightly less favorite?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "he", "prefer", "the", "Newt", "Gingrich", "today", "to", "the", "one", "that", "he", "found", "slightly", "less", "favorite", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJR", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Newt Gingrich"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 602, "question": "What would your mother make of you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "your", "mother", "make", "of", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 603, "answer": "Oh, my mother would just love me.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "my", "mother", "would", "just", "love", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "Do you feel like you've almost spent the last 50 years bracing yourself for this week and this battle?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "like", "you", "'ve", "almost", "spent", "the", "last", "50", "years", "bracing", "yourself", "for", "this", "week", "and", "this", "battle", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "Yes, in a sense.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "in", "a", "sense", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last 50 years"]}}]